hey everybody well comes it is the one in
which the listening project this video
you can use this video the practically you
listening and comprehension is icepeak
you ready cd other branch that doctors
apartments
this is after of my favorite topics that cheese
honestly aichi corentin the doctor
amsterdam if you can simply guys would
be on this one and real-time have for
the doctor ranga nervus accessorius cat
white a language and rescue's over but not
set with stokkel that we the what the
processes threw the doctor in the us to
first of all it's important to talk
about helping turns in us most people
help in shirts picasso dali
the custom getting merkel creamy candy
astronomical
with the silent problem here the
christian church itself as a closets
were man
if you single and you justin sharing
yourself the effort costs per month is
want we 300 everything
however if you and sharing the familiar
which has this over
can you that is cool man in new window the
page you money money for your mouth i
premium
you silent have it a nice way to your
work sligo the doctors office it's crazy
ya know you  might be thinking white
people they deathmatch way this
is not get helps interns well that dark
doctor much and i don't need any major
operations ropes that fine life
centimeter havens theories getting an
action in europe etal are his thousands of
dollars tickettribune python him shows
syria my opinion the downsides marine
insurance in the us is the mixer view
cover for any major unexpected events
news with sticks what the doctor's
office must now become we now doctor of
the first time the receptionist iso
limit iv years for with all your pers
medical history of europe training day
shion todo not does is super for you
see the doctor you can i too d'n urste
measure your high grade and blood
pressure
samsung gear nervous the doctor's office
my blood pressure reading is usually
haar my ethics
so fond of pure students who a high
blood pressure absolutely iq measurements
and everything they leave you other
maloney you have something for the doctor the
kam ben youth league there were 14 min a
consultation with the doctor and hopefully
something productive
of course ipad mini japanese mens in my
life dry power and more productive was
really depends  on where you go and which
tac toy okay so leslie the doctor white
superscript chinese not won in your cup
medication in the pharmacy
as well as juni the cs specialist the doctors
for you to one and then you said there a
point it mean you can decide for marloes
who as if the private practice doctors
the fed nemesis alcide and so general
system
the usually much more flexible in channel
for better care with the resources on more
ltd
okay that will for the they leave a comment
elmi hammetje doctors the pony costs in
your country
if your neck is standing
[Music]
[Applause]